tataindicombroadband.in 2009-02-17

# Tata Indicom Broadband

Privacy Policy

In the course of using this website or availing the products and services vide the online application forms and questionnaires, Tata Communications and its Affiliates may become privy to the personal information of its customers, including information that is of a confidential nature.

Tata Communications is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its customers and has taken all necessary and reasonable measures to protect the confidentiality of the customer information and its transmission through the web. While no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure from intrusion, we have used and will continue to use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the protection of your information.

The Customer would be required to cooperate with Tata Communications in order to ensure the security of the information, and it is recommended that the Customers necessarily choose their passwords carefully such that no unauthorised access is made by a third party. To make the password complex and difficult for others to guess, the Customers should use combination of alphabets, numbers and special characters (like !, @, #, $ etc.). The Customers should undertake not to disclose their password to anyone or keep any written or other record of the password such that a third party could access it.

Tata Communications undertakes not to disclose the information provided by the Customers to any person, unless such action is necessary to: 

  * Conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; 
  * Protect and defend Tata Communications's or its Affiliates' rights, interests or property; 
  * Enforce the terms and conditions of the products or services; or 
  * Act to protect the interests of Tata Communications, its Affiliates, or its members, constituents or of other persons. 

The Customers shall not disclose to any other person, in any manner whatsoever, any information relating to Tata Communications or its Affiliates of a confidential nature obtained in the course of availing the services through the website. Failure to comply with this obligation shall be deemed a serious breach of the terms herein and shall entitle Tata Communications or its Affiliates to terminate the services, without prejudice to any damages, to which the customer may be entitled otherwise. 

Tata Communications will limit the collection and use of customer information only on a need-to-know basis to deliver better service to the customers. Tata Communications may use and share the information provided by the Customers with its Affiliates and third parties for providing services and any service-related activities such as collecting subscription fees for such services, and notifying or contacting the Customers regarding any problem with, or the expiration of, such services. In this regard, it may be necessary to disclose the customer information to one or more agents and contractors of Tata Communications and their sub-contractors, but such agents, contractors, and sub-contractors will be required to agree to use the information obtained from Tata Communications only for these purposes.

Our Site may contain advertisements, references and links to other web sites and organizations. We may also use third parties to display or serve advertising on the Site and our web-based newsletters. Often these third party advertising companies employ cookie and web bug technologies to measure advertising effectiveness. You should be aware that different rules may apply to the collection, use or disclosure of your information by third parties in connection with their advertisements, promotions and other web sites you encounter on the Internet. The use of such technology by these third parties is within their control and not ours, and even if we have a relationship with the third party, we do not control those sites or their policies and practices regarding your information and we encourage you to investigate and ask questions directly of them in this regard.

The Customer authorises Tata Communications to exchange, share, part with all information related to the details and transaction history of the Customers to its Affiliates / banks / financial institutions / credit bureaus / agencies/participation in any telecommunication or electronic clearing network as may be required by law, customary practice, credit reporting, statistical analysis and credit scoring, verification or risk management and shall not hold Tata Communications liable for use or disclosure of this information.

Tata Communications will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect company and customer feedback. When Tata Communications posts changes to this Statement, you will see the word "updated" next to the Privacy Statement link on the front page of Tata Communications. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how Tata Communications will use your personal information, Tata Communications will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. Tata Communications encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how we are protecting your information.
